<?xml version = "1.0"?>
<!-- key -->
<!-- korean -->
<!-- jpn -->
<!-- chinese -->
<!-- enu -->
<blocks>
	<keys num_keys="5" key1="key" key2="korean" key3="jpn" key4="chinese" key5="enu" />
	<block key="BK_0_0000_Name" korean="Book a test" />
	<block key="BK_0_0000_description" korean="The test for the book." />
	<block key="BK_0_0000_text" korean="Oh ...! Nourish you ... can not believe it! Find me hustle risk're here ... to here.\n\u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e\nI have a wicked day Brage Fire Golem and cattle were kept occupied this place, to prevent the gate. I continued else do you think you need help to escape the forest spirits.\n\u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e\nHao notify you as soon as possible so that the news of the kingdom of His Majesty in Pomerania princess." />
	<block key="BK_0_0001_Name" korean="Taming the primer (Wolves)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0001_description" korean="The way the wolves how this is stated." />
	<block key="BK_0_0001_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame a wolf \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Common Wolf \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e common wolves without a special preparation can easily tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0001_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Elite Class wolf \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class of ordinary city can not tame wolf by nature violent. Feed the prey of wild boar Guy Okay, let's try to tame After you create a good mood. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0001_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Epic Wolf \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e Like an epic wolf wolf also with the elite class, and if you try to tame fed your favorite feed back. However, only the rare epic wolf ate wild boar, before feeling the threat of death, let's keep in mind that a person who does not eat the food." />
	<block key="BK_0_0002_Name" korean="Taming the primer (Shadow Wolf)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0002_description" korean="The way how the shadow wolves are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0002_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame a wolf shadow \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Common shadow wolf \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e shadow wolf vigilance is high, it is difficult to catch a tame opportunities. Shadow Wolf only when you eat the food Solving the boundary, he eats meat only special aura of darkness imbued. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0002_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Shadow Wolf elite class \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class, except the dark shadows of the spirit wolf eats only meat contained significantly more simply, a typical shadow wolf and the way they are shown the way. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cBr \u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0002_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Epic Shadow Wolf \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic shadow wolf, eat only the meat of animals with strong Dark attribute, before feeling the threat of death should note that the people who eat the food is." />
	<block key="BK_0_0003_Name" korean="Taming the primer (Lynx flow)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0003_description" korean="Lynx Motorcycles (leopards, lions, tigers, etc.) to tame methods are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0003_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame a wildcat current is \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. General wildcat flow \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e general wildcat error is without a special preparation can easily tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0003_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Elite class wildcat kind \u003c/ b\u003e Lynx kind of elite class does not count when \u003cbr\u003e usual tame by nature violent. Feeding of cattle feed that they had been right, let's try to tame After you create a good mood. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0003_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Like the epic kind lynx \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic Lynx lynx current flow is also an elite class, and if you try to tame fed your favorite feed back. However, an epic kind lynx is eating the rare lesser curvature, before feeling the threat of death, let's keep in mind that a person who does not eat the food." />
	<block key="BK_0_0004_Name" korean="Taming the primer (Bear)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0004_description" korean="The way how the bears are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0004_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame a bear \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. General bear \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e general bear without a special preparation can easily tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0004_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Elite class bear \u003c/ b\u003e elite class can not bear upon \u003cbr\u003e normal is tame by nature violent. Feeding the reindeer feed Guy Okay, let's try to tame made you feel better after. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0004_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Epic Bear \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic bear bear as well as the elite class, and if you try to tame fed your favorite feed back. However, only a rare epic bear is eating reindeer, before feeling the threat of death, let's keep in mind that a person who does not eat the food." />
	<block key="BK_0_0005_Name" korean="Taming the primer (wild boar)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0005_description" korean="The way how this is stated that the wild boar." />
	<block key="BK_0_0005_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame a wild boar \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Common Warthog \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e common warthog is ready without special can easily tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0005_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Because the elite class boar \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class has the power Boar very century, after a physical place down somewhat, you should try to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0005_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Epic boar \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e Like an epic wild boar and even the elite class boar, placed behind the lower the fitness, you should try to tame. However, it will be chaining down a lot more stamina than the elite class boar." />
	<block key="BK_0_0006_Name" korean="Taming the primer (small)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0006_description" korean="This is the way how the cattle are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0006_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame the cattle \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Typical small \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e common cattle without a special preparation is easy to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0006_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Because small elite class \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e very small elite class is the force strength, stamina put back down somewhat, you should try to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0006_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Like an epic cattle \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic Soto small elite class, placed behind the lower the fitness, you should try to tame. However, it will be chaining down a lot more stamina than the small elite class." />
	<block key="BK_0_0007_Name" korean="Taming the primer (spider)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0007_description" korean="The way how the spiders are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0007_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame the spider \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. In order to tame the common spider \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e spider, the spider venom with aura has to be suppressed. After the suppression strength of spider venom poison in the lower atmosphere suppression order, let's try to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0007_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Because the elite class spider \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class spider venom strong energy than a regular spider venom should be used for intermediate energy suppression order. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0007_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Epic spider \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e poison aura with an epic spider venom higher energy suppression orders can be suppressed only with each other. However, because the city has heard the usual order due to the power of an epic spider, let's put down after the order to spend a lot of stamina." />
	<block key="BK_0_0008_Name" korean="Taming the primer (reindeer)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0008_description" korean="How are the reindeer way they are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0008_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame the reindeer is \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. General reindeer \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e general preparation without the need for special reindeer can easily tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0008_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Elite Class reindeer \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class does not obey stubborn reindeer processor easily put down after the physical extent, should try to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0008_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Like an epic reindeer \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic reindeer reindeer even the elite class, placed behind the lower the fitness, you should try to tame. However, it will be chaining down a lot more stamina than the elite class reindeer." />
	<block key="BK_0_0009_Name" korean="Taming the primer (modified reindeer antlers)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0009_description" korean="Modify reindeer antlers way that they are written way." />
	<block key="BK_0_0009_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e Edit tame reindeer antlers how \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Typical modifications reindeer antlers \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e modify reindeer antlers vigilance is high, it is difficult to catch a tame opportunities. The reindeer antlers modified to solve the boundary only when you eat the food, he eats Pullman containing mysterious Dust. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0009_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Elite Class modify reindeer antlers \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class modified reindeer horns, with the exception Dust eat the Pullman contained much more is just, and tame reindeer antlers common modifications as the method. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0009_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Epic modify reindeer antlers \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic modify reindeer antlers, sparkly eat Pullman contained so many Dust day, before feeling the threat of death should note that the people who eat the food is." />
	<block key="BK_0_0010_Name" korean="Taming the introduction (the turtle)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0010_description" korean="The way how the turtles are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0010_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame a turtle \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Common turtle \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e common turtle without a special preparation can easily tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0010_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Elite Class Turtle \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class processor stubborn turtle does not submit easily, after a physical place down somewhat, you should try to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0010_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Like an epic turtles \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic turtle turtle is also an elite class, after lowering the physical place, you should try to tame. However, it will be chaining down a lot more stamina than the elite class turtles." />
	<block key="BK_0_0011_Name" korean="Taming the primer (say)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0011_description" korean="Way to say that the way this is written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0011_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame horses \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Common words \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e common words without the need for special preparation is easy to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0011_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Elite-class horse \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class does not obey the stubborn horse processor easily put down after the physical extent, should try to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0011_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Epic Horse \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic nonsense words as well as the elite class, placed behind the lower the fitness, you should try to tame. However, it will be chaining down a lot more stamina than the end of the elite class." />
	<block key="BK_0_0012_Name" korean="Taming the primer (Unicorn)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0012_description" korean="Unicorn way how they are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0012_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame the unicorn is \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. General Unicorn \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e Unicorn vigilance is high, it is difficult to catch a tame opportunities. Unicorns only eat the food when it is to solve the boundary, the guy who grew up eating Pullman mysterious dew. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0012_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Unicorn elite class \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class unicorn, except eat faded grown Pullman clear dew is simply no tea, unicorns and the way they are as a general way." />
	<block key="BK_0_0012_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 3. Epic Unicorn \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic mystical unicorns eat Pullman consisting of dew, before feeling the threat of death should note that the people who eat the food is." />
	<block key="BK_0_0013_Name" korean="Taming the tutorial (The Firebird)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0013_description" korean="Phoenix is ​​the way how they are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0013_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame the Phoenix is ​​\u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Common Phoenix \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e general Phoenix is ​​without special preparation can easily tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0013_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Phoenix elite class \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e Phoenix elite class does not submit easily stubborn processor, put down after the physical extent, you should try to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0013_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Like the epic Phoenix \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e epic Phoenix Phoenix is ​​also an elite class, placed behind the lower the fitness, you should try to tame. However, it will be chaining down a lot more stamina than the elite class Phoenix." />
	<block key="BK_0_0014_Name" korean="Taming the primer (monster)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0014_description" korean="Road monster with attributes, how they are written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0014_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame the monster is \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. Common monster \u003c/ b\u003e to tame the \u003cbr\u003e monster, monsters, it is necessary to suppress the property with aura. The opposite attribute value of the property with a monster behind somewhat placed, Let suppressing properties aura aura to lower property suppression order. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0014_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. Elite-level monsters \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e elite class in order to suppress the property aura of monsters, you can use the intermediate properties aura suppression order. However, in order to use the intermediate energy suppressing properties orders, should put a lot of monsters are having the opposite attribute levels and lowering a lot of stamina should prevent resistance in order." />
	<block key="BK_0_0014_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 3. Epic monster \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e hero must use a higher strength properties suppression order to tame the monster class. Order using conditions similar to when the elite class tame monsters, but even more to raise objections property value, and physical and should be lowered much more." />
	<block key="BK_0_0015_Name" korean="Taming the tutorial (which is the master monster)" />
	<block key="BK_0_0015_description" korean="Ownership way the monsters in this way they will be written." />
	<block key="BK_0_0015_text" korean="\u003cB\u003e tame the monster that the master is how \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 1. General monster masters \u003c/ b\u003e If you have a monster gildeulyiryeo \u003cbr\u003e owners, the bond is released when removing the master. For normal monsters, and is released when the bond owners fall into chaos because for a while, that would be easy to tame. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0015_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 2. When the elite class in the elite class monster monster \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e owners owners lose the Master, just like a normal monster, and it is possible to tame. When the bond between the owner of a long fall off for a while confusing, but let's note quickly recovered. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0015_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cB\u003e 3. Epic Monster \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e owner tame the monster that this is an epic way to the master degree, the general monsters tame, but significantly different from what, so care must be taken because the owner is a strong opponent of the epic. In addition, the epic monsters do not fall into chaos and even release the bond owner." />
	<block key="BK_0_0016_Name" korean="Torn bear sanyangbeop book" />
	<block key="BK_0_0016_description" korean="How to tame a ragged tattered books written on the bear" />
	<block key="BK_0_0016_text" korean="Torn bear sanyangbeop book" />
	<block key="BK_0_0016_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e How to tame the giant bear \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e\nThus, using a two-stage giant bear is bound to jump the way they are. \u003cbr\u003e First need to tame tame Fellow in common.\n\u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e\nThis specifies the target of a huge bear up to Fellow status by Tan and jump and jump while on board the fellow again after using the taming skill. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e\nQuick wits are required, but if you want to have a big fellow is sure to learn how." />
	<block key="BK_0_0017_Name" korean="Diary of a lighthouse keeper." />
	<block key="BK_0_0017_description" korean="Adventurers went down the harbor lighthouse keeper diary is written in a hurry before closing" />
	<block key="BK_0_0017_text" korean="Diary of a lighthouse keeper." />
	<block key="BK_0_0017_text_attach_0" korean="\u003cB\u003e 00 년 00 days weather Clear \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e suddenly people started collapsing. Touching those bizarre body protruding, who was attacked by the body is continuing this nightmare again falling. Does where they come from? Walk to the lighthouse door locks firmly hold, but do not know where to go. \u003cbr\u003e \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0017_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 00 년 00 days weather rain \u003c/ b\u003e The voice of the daughter \u003cbr\u003e sounds outside the door. Is hallucinations? Or Are you really my daughter? \u003cbr\u003e my daughter, if I can not snapped up by those monsters. Be sure of saving. Yeah, I'll open the door! \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0017_text_attach_2" korean="\u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 00 년 00 days weather rain \u003c/ b\u003e \u003cbr\u003e 죽는다.죽는다.죽는다.죽는다.나는죽는다.죽는다.죽는다.죽는다.나는죽는다.죽는다.…. \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0017_text_attach_3" korean="\u003cbr\u003e \u003cb\u003e 00 년 00 days weather rain \u003c/ b\u003e I turn out the light of \u003cbr\u003e lighthouse. Everyone should know that. The end rugged adventurer harbor. To reveal the truth. I have seen the terrible events of the culprit of the town .... (Not recognizable) \u003cbr\u003e" />
	<block key="BK_0_0018_Name" korean="History of the Bell jeroseu" />
	<block key="BK_0_0018_description" korean="Bell jeroseu less articles" />
	<block key="BK_0_0018_text" korean="History of the Bell jeroseu" />
	<block key="BK_0_0018_text_attach_0" korean="Born in the land. Ads will be in hell. Land forces crossed the sky looks ominous weakness. Jealousy turns disastrous betrayal is called a disastrous failure." />
	<block key="BK_0_0018_text_attach_1" korean="One \u003cbr\u003e warrior solve everything up bunyeonhi that veterans will never be alone." />
	<block key="BK_0_0018_text_attach_2" korean="\u003cbr\u003e Beware of all veterans. Before killing the true warrior warrior false." />
	<block key="BK_0_0018_text_attach_3" korean="The power of \u003cbr\u003e Ellora've made for the golden goddess, now we shall have our commitment to Ellora." />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_Name" korean="Earl document tree lights" />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_description" korean="Paper presented to the airspace of destruction" />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_text" korean="Earl document tree lights" />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_text_attach_0" korean="Time ally of the light incident mix of myth and reality are one, and all such information is recorded by the clash of Ellora goddess gel Naris tree that lights Earl's destruction." />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_text_attach_1" korean="\u003cbr\u003e airspace of the current destruction is actually a very powerful Ellora's strength and the power of darkness and keep it crashes because nothing seems to have emerged all the land of airspace." />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_text_attach_2" korean="\u003cbr\u003e power of Ellora often thought it would be more powerful it becomes gel inside to push the power of eminent scientists Naris. However, according to the announcement of the Glacier door itself is essential to maintain the balance of airspace collapse and destruction if this is a serious Canas Kingdom can cause damage." />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_text_attach_3" korean="If added \u003cbr\u003e according to the power of Ellora are conjugate, we are of the horse and Canas priest expects to collapse, unlike airspace." />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_text_attach_4" korean="\u003cbr\u003e exception is only one, and if the strength of the gel Naris stronger. If you ever want to use the airspace of destruction appear less strongly to Ellora will be one of the goddess of strength or gel strength or weakness Naris tteuriryeo down the balance and Canas will only need to balance among its many variables." />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_text_attach_5" korean="For \u003cbr\u003e it should constitute a permanent presence as knights and suggests that the voracious be composed of the price of power in flight Fellow." />
	<block key="BK_0_0019_text_attach_6" korean="\u003cbr\u003e excimer company's ohseolri" />
</blocks>
